Alright, now the second test case. So,
Tudo bem, agora o segundo caso de teste. Ento, para economizar
to save time, I'm going to duplicate this test method.
tempo, vou duplicar esse mtodo de teste.
And change the test method name to
E altere o
BookingStartsBeforeAndFinishes
nome do mtodo
InTheMiddleOf
de teste para
AnExistingBooking. In this case we have overlap,
BookingStartsBeforeAndFinishes InTheMiddleOf AnExistingBooking. Nesse caso,
so, this method should ReturnExisting
temos sobreposio, portanto, esse
BookingsReference.
mtodo deve ReturnExisting BookingsReference.
Okay, now, let's modify the logic
Ok, agora vamos modificar a
here. So we can have this new booking start
lgica aqui. Assim, podemos ter este novo incio
before the existing booking we don't need this argument here.
de reserva antes da reserva existente, no precisamos deste argumento aqui.
and to simulate the middle of scenario
e para simular o meio do
we can call the after method, so After
cenrio, podemos chamar o mtodo after,
ExistingBookings.ArrivalDate. Now, we need to
ento After ExistingBookings. Data de chegada. Agora, precisamos afirmar
Assert that Result is EqualTo a,
que o resultado  igual a, mas algum que
but someone reading this code may wonder, "what is a, where did that
l este cdigo pode se perguntar: "o que ,
come from?" So a better way to write this Assertion,
de onde veio isso? "Ento, uma maneira melhor de
is like this. We want to make sure that this result is equal
escrever essa afirmao  assim. Queremos ter certeza de que esse resultado
ToExistingBooking.Reference. Whatever that is.
seja igual a ToExistingBooking. Referncia. Seja l o que .
Let's run this test.
Vamos rodar esse teste.
Okay, our test passed, beautiful. In the next
Ok, nosso teste passou, lindo. Na prxima aula,
lecture, we'll look at another test case.
veremos outro caso de teste.